So today let's go, the moot is a little stuck, not a little, it is a
lot stuck, but right now it is
standing at the back, I will show you that, be careful, after seeing it
you all have already come to know, so
how did this accident happen, Papa, I mean
due to whom did the accident happen, I will give you all the
details, now I am not in the gas pot, I am
telling you what Thapa said, take a look at the
scooter cold look once, you are
seeing this panel, it is completely gone,
along with it this panel is also gone,
it is broken from here and this is gone
and look at this at the back, a bomb has exploded from here, you see,
I will have to change this also,
this entire portion, this portion and this
question, what is happening from this corner,
look at the house light, it is going up and down, so this has happened, the
condition of my Chotu, for
how long has this happened, that is why when was you
coming to the office, I had installed two batteries, it was
completed, it was completed,
finally Papa was going to get the second one, he went to
that link and directly hit it here, straight away.  I have hit it, what should I
say, drink and drive is
already very, very good, I mean the news is that
this nozzle is ready that don't drink and
drive, I don't know why people drink and drive, or
scooter, or bike,
it is very dangerous for them too,
and the most maintenance is
very high for the people passing by, because now you will
not feel any pain at that time, the pain will
not be free, but the
brother of the person you hit will suffer a lot, or if such an
accident has happened, I mean, thank God,
nothing has happened to my father because there was mud on the site
itself, my father fell on it, he did
not get any injury,
but only that, but now think, if it was
not mud, if there was some
way to climb there, what would have happened, so all this
means I am getting angry, but still, what should I say now, I do
n't have to say anything, it had become half
popular, if you ask these people for something, I mean,
damage, I mean, give me money, friend, if you
cannot ask for something like this, then what should I
say,
speechless please  Like judges
riding bikes of Lokpal is Naxalism or
riding a scooter, so whatever development you want, please don't
ride it, PK, by any alternative, it is
not free from danger, it has been very dangerous for a long time,
today it happened to my father, tomorrow it could have happened to
someone's father or it could have happened to
me as well, if what should I
say, my mind is not working, it
means so much, it is so good and I love it so much, with
this color, with this graphic,
you people will think that I bought
this by selling sports medicine, so
airplane mode is off,
now if the work is at least two-three things,
two-three things that I will improve,
after going to the showroom, if I see that everything is within my budget, then after
seeing the money, I will get it repaired,
otherwise if it costs too much, then
I will make an insurance claim, apart from that
I have
no other way because
looking at the damage, looking at the damage,
I feel that it will cost around five to six thousand,
after that
you can edit the limit charge  Look, everyone is going to be cheated of Rs 6000
because of a ginger rider. I will not give my opinion. I will take my opinion.
I will not give my opinion
because riders do not do such work.
People who are professional writers have done it and
nothing else. The song is that
now ideally there is no
scratch or dent at any place. It is a little bit at
this place because father had
fallen on this set and there was a side effect and the
fourth part fell off. Because of this,
look here there is a little sketch, this Miller I
applied that day and it was broken. This Miller
also has a scratch and there are
mothers
and there is no complaint at any place.
It is just the main damage to the scooter that is
here.
What should I say friend, such a great graphics. I do
n't know whether the yoga officer will definitely
come exactly the same or not.
[Music]
I am the waste man
and tell me Saurabh and the thing is that I just
want to say that please don't drink and
drive, don't drink and drive because
your own life is in danger and
you are putting the life of others
in danger as well.  So it is okay that
you do not have control over your bike at that
time, don't do this, friend, don't do this, there is
no benefit in doing this,
you will not get anything, on the contrary, your life will be ruined, all this will be
ruined,
now let's go, let's get rid of it,
after that we will see what to do, now
I went to the showroom but did
not make any video, I was in a very off mood, madam, I have only one
request, this is very close to my heart,
Swaran, I was in a very off mood, I left it, I made an
insurance claim because there were
huge expenses,
around 100, okay, for this I will think, let's go, I feel
confident, I will get the work done, then
Chotu is at my house, the day the pass
etc. will come because I knew it already
because I have played it, but it will not be valid,
especially this color 100 school subject
parts, everything will be charged only after the day it comes, it will
not be charged before that, that is why Chotu is
lying at my house, now what should I do, I am
not able to go out with him, there is a lot of
problem because most of the things used at home are for the bike
That is causing a lot of
problems but I am lucky that
nothing has happened, I just forget this thing,
guys please do
not drive the bike, whatever is parked, friend, if you find
someone driving a bike after drinking alcohol in front of you
or someone standing in front of you and driving the bike, doing something like this, then
first
say something to him or go to the police, only after that it
is okay, if all this does not work, what do I mean, if you do not say anything, you will be
cheated of seven thousand rupees, that first we will have to take it,
after that it will be sent to this company, then you will
see, okay, the money is fine, the money will come,
but if anything happens in life,
anything happens, and if I had a fracture in my leg, I would have gone to the
backstreet, friend, if
anything had happened, then think about how much more damage it would have caused,
so please do not drink, you just want to drink, there is nothing else to
say, you do not get anything on the other side
[Music]
do it
[Music] do it
[Praise]
[Music]